本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
注意力集中  副警长  别忘了你的训练
Focus, deputy. Remember your trainin'.
放松  放松
Easy, easy...
就快成功了
You're almost there.
可恶  我差点就拿到宝藏了
Dang it! I almost got the treasure!
我们在一起的时光就是宝藏
The time we spend together is treasure enough.
嘿  你感觉到了吗
Hey! You feel that?
感觉我们应该报告这件事
Reckon we should report that.
或者坐我们的新敞篷汽车兜兜风
Or go for a ride in our new convertible!
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
CC录制： ufohaman  Qin Cong
时间轴： shortcut  Enpistu
■
翻译： wesyman  Chamania
校订  后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第一季第十八集
Gravity Falls  S01E18  Land Before Swine
女士们  先生们
Ladies and Gentlemen,
让我们继续神秘的旅行
Continuing our mystery tour,
你会看到世界著名的神秘厕所
You'll see the world famous outhouse of mystery.
我曾经被困在里面过
I got stuck in there once!
我可以上厕所吗
Could I go to the bathroom?
问题等到旅程结束再问
Save all questions until after the tour.
往前直走  如果你靠近看的话
And up ahead if you look really closely--
每个人把照相机拿出来
Everybody get your cameras,
你们会希望看到这个的
You're gonna want to see this...
摇摇  终于啊
Finally, Waddles,
我们可以统治整个屋子啦
We have the whole house to ourselves!
你觉得来个舞会怎么样
What do you think, dance party?
我没听到说不哦
I'm not hearing a no!
到抱抱时间了  哈哈哈
Uh-oh, cuddle time. Ha ha ha!
摇摇  我可以跟你说个秘密吗
Waddles, can I tell you a secret?
你是我全世界最喜欢的猪
You're my favorite pig in the whole world.
梅宝  你在地板上做什么呢
Mabel! What are you doing on the floor?
做可爱的好孩子
Being cute and great.
我还以为你弟弟就够怪的了
And I thought your brother was weird.
不  他更像是 “噢  我们来解开秘密”
No, he's more like, "Oh! Let's solve a mystery!
我亲枕头  枕头上画了温蒂的脸
I kiss a pillow with Wendy's face drawn on it."
哈哈  学得真像  亲枕头
Ha ha! That's pretty good! Kissin' a pillow.
加油  把裤腿吃掉
Go! Go! Chew that pant leg!
好吧  给我出去  马上
All right, outside. Now!
不行  斯坦叔公
No! Grunkle Stan!
摇摇在外面不安全
It's not safe for waddles outside.
外面有食肉动物  还有吃烧烤的人
There's predators! And barbecuers!
这是大自然的法则
That's just the natural order.
你的小猪好吃又不是我的错
It's not my fault your pig's potentially delicious.
他应该像人一样呆在屋里头
He should be inside like a person.
人才不会浑身脏兮兮地到处打滚
People don't roll around in their own filth.
除了苏斯
Except for Soos.
这点我们还不如摇摇
And we're the lesser for it!
或许应该是我们呆在屋外
Maybe we're the ones who should be put outside.
是不是  考虑一下吧
Huh? Huh? Think about it!
苏斯  成败就在今天  谢谢你来参加本次任务
Today's the day, Soos. Thanks for coming along on this mission.
哥们儿  这是我的荣耀
Dude, it's an honor.
今天我流着炎热和兴奋的汗水
Today I'm sweating from heat and excitement.
这个树林里隐藏着某个东西
There's something hiding in these woods.
某种大到能撕裂汽车车顶的东西
Something big enough to rip the roof off a car.
如果我们拍到这东西的照片  我们就是英雄啦
If we get a photo of this thing, we'll be heroes!
对  到时会有好多美女
Yeah, we'll get all the babes.
你得用木棍挡开她们  不让她们抱上来亲你
You'll be fending off smooches with a stick!
哈哈  住嘴  伙计
Ha ha! Shut up, man.
用木棍  伙计
With a stick, dude.
来  给我帮帮忙
Here. Give me a boost.
搞定
Oof! Got it.
呃  树脂有这么粘吗
Uhh. Is sap supposed to be this sticky?
如果一切按照计划进展的话
If everything goes according to plan,
这个生物会抓住那牛排
The creature will grab that steak,
穿过这些绳索
Cross through the string,
于是就会启动照相机A  B  C
And set off cameras a, b, and c.
绝对不会出差错
And nothing can go wrong.
击掌
High five.
这真是计划不周
This was poorly planned.
-嘿  你  -说我吗
- Hey, you! - Me?
-还在为经常弄摔宝宝苦恼吗  -是的
-Sick of constantly dropping your baby? -Yes!
嗨  我是鲍比・伦佐比
Hi! I'm Bobby Renzobbi,
你需要的是“抱抱有爱婴儿背带”
And what you need is the huggy wuvvy tummy bundle!
我能一次背十个宝宝
I can hold ten babies at once!
我知道你在想什么 “可以给猪用吗”
I know what you're thinkin'-- "Does it work for pigs?"
当然  猪也能用  白痴
Yeah, it does work for pigs, stupid!
贴身感受你的猪的心跳
Feel your pig's heartbeat next to yours!
猪也能用
It works for p-I-I-I-I-gs!
斯坦叔公
Grunkle Stan!
我要去买“抱抱有爱婴儿背带”
I'm off to get a huggy wuvvy tummy bundle!
受不了  给猪织情侣毛衣还嫌不够吗
Yeesh! Isn't knitting matching sweaters for that pig enough?
不够  不管怎样  在我不在的时候
Nope. Anyway, I need you to look after
我需要你帮我照顾这位小先生
This little gentleman while I'm gone.
孩子  现在不行  有旅客要过来参观
Not now, kid. I got some tourists comin' through.
斯坦叔公  我知道你不是很喜欢摇摇
Grunkle Stan, I know you're not crazy about Waddles.
他是个又胖  又不穿衣服的蠢猪
He's a fat, naked jerk!
但是你最关心我了
But you do care about me.
答应我你不会把他放到外面去的
Promise me you won't let him outside?
行  好好  我答应
Fine! Yeah, yeah, I promise.
谢谢你  斯坦叔公
Thanks, Grunkle Stan!
我看着你呢  猪头
I'm watching you, pig.
我们成功了  它被绳索绊到了
We did it! It tripped the wire!
这些照相机里会有这个生物的照片
Somewhere in these cameras is a photo of that creature!
我去处理胶卷
I'll go develop the film.
我去做胜利玉米片
I'll go make us victory nachos.
迪普和苏斯是一辈子的搭档
Dipper and Soos for life!
女士们先生们  这里
And here, ladies and gentlemen,
是我们最后的展品
Is our final exhibit,
人类已知最丑陋的生物
The most hideous creatures known to man!
噢  是我们
Oh, it's us!
好的  好的  我们
Right, right. We...
我们玩笑已经开过了
We have fun here.
但说真的  大伙们
But seriously, folks,
这是个了不起的东西
This is something.
我向你们呈现
I present to you
用玉米做成的独角兽
A unicorn made out of corn:
玉米角兽
The cornicorn!
谁知道呢  我已经厌倦了
I-I don't know. I'm tired.
搞什么
What the--?!
太坑人了
What a rip-off!
孩子们  我们走
Kids, we're leaving.
不  不要
No! Noooo!
你
Grrr. You!
拜托  拜托
Come on, come on...
这是翅膀
That's a wing!
如果相机B拍到翅膀的话
If camera b got the wing,
拍到其余部位的相机应该是
Then the one that should have got the rest is...
相机C
Camera c!
那生物
The creature!
谁想来点胜利玉米片
Who wants victory nachos?
不
No!
伙计  别担心
Dude, don't worry.
我只吃了大约三分之一
I only ate like a third of 'em.
一半
Half of 'em.
我把他们全吃了  伙计
I ate all of 'em, dude.
只不过让这头猪在屋外呆十分钟
Just ten minutes without this pig in the house,
这不算过分吧
Is that so much to ask?
喂  如果梅宝问起来的话
There. If Mabel asks...
这件事从来没有发生过
This never happened.
噢  斯坦叔公  但是外面不安全
"Oh, but Grunkle Stan! It's not safe out there!
外面有食肉动物  噢  拜托
There's predators!" Oh, brother.
我不敢相信你会做出这种事   伙计
I can't believe you, man!
抱歉  哥们  我太亢奋了  玉米片会导致亢奋
Sorry, dude. I was just so excited! Nachos cause excitement.
苏斯  无意冒犯  但是你有时真的得小心一点
Soos, no offense, but you gotta be more careful sometimes.
我的意思是  我们要
I'm mean, what are the
再拍到这样一张照片有多难
odds we'll ever get another picture of the--
伙计  你看到了吗
Dude, did you see that?
这东西是条恐龙  哥们儿
That thing was a dinosaur, bro!
恐龙怎么能生存六千五百万年呢
How is it possible a dinosaur survived 65 million years?
派恩斯先生  你看到了吗
Did you see it, Mr. Pines?
-派恩斯先生  -它
- Mr. Pines? - It--
-它把他带走了  -带走了什么
- It took him. - Took what?
那头猪  它带走了摇摇
The pig. It took Waddles.
你刚才说摇摇怎么了
What'd you say about waddles?
尴尬的沉默
Oh, whoa. Awkward silence.
发生什么了  你们都站这儿干嘛  摇摇去哪了
What's going on? Why are you standing around and where's Waddles?
好消息是  你马上要有一条小狗了
The good news is, you're gettin' a puppy!
-发生什么了  -好吧  你瞧
- What happened? - Well, see,
呃  当时
Uh, when the--
那头猪被玉龙吃掉了  哥们儿
The pig got eaten by a p-terodactyl, bro.
什么
What?!
摇摇  摇摇
Waddles? Waddles!
他去哪了  为什么会发生这种事
Where did he go?! How did this happen?!
斯坦叔公  你没有把他放到屋外吧
Grunkle Stan, you didn't put him outside?
什么  没有  我哪里都没放
What?! No! I didn't put him anywhere!
我的表现一点都不可疑
I'm not acting suspicious!
你的表现很可疑
You're acting suspicious!
-猪是什么回事  -然后发生了什么
- What's a pig?! - Then what happened?
呃  瞧  事情是这样的
Uh, look, it went down like this, see?
当时  我在客厅里
So there I was, in the living room...
温柔地用最上等的奶油伺候他
Tenderly nursing him with only the richest of creams,
就在那时  突然
When all of a sudden...
于是我说
So I said...
没门儿  牛仔
Aaah! No dice, cowboy!
我开始朝他的脸猛打
I start punching him right in the face!
但是他使用肮脏的伎俩
But he played dirty.
事情就是这样
That really happened.
为什么  为什么你不带走我
Why?! Why couldn't you have taken me?!!!
斯坦叔公  你努力要救他
Oh, Grunkle Stan, you tried to save him!
呃  是的  我是个伟人  好吧
Uh, yep. I'm a... great man, all right.
你一拳打到翼龙脸上
You punched a pterodactyl in the face?
我以为你压根不相信超自然的东西
I thought you didn't even believe in the supernatural.
恐龙又不是魔法  它们只不过是大蜥蜴
Dinosaurs aren't magic. They're just big lizards.
少跟我嗦
Get off my back!
噢  摇摇
Oh, Waddles.
够了
That's it.
招惹我姐姐  就算是翼龙也不行
No pterodactyl messes with my sister.
我们去那边抓住他  然后把你的猪救出来
We're gonna go out there, catch him, and save your pig.
为了梅宝  伙计们
For Mabel, guys!
为了梅宝
For Mabel!
但我们怎么才能找到这个小家伙
But how do we even find the little guy?
我们跟着那个
We follow that!
太棒了  真是天才
Oh, sweet! Yes! Genius!
或者  你瞧  我们今天可以收工了
Or, ya know, we could just call it a day,
或许打打台球  或许  呃
Maybe hit the pool hall or, uh...
对  我们出发
Yeah! Let's go...
救出挠挠
Save waggles!
- 是摇摇  - 他也救
- Waddles. - Him too.
好了
All right!
那个玉龙不会知道是什么东西打他的
That p-terodactyl won't know what hit him.
呃  是“翼龙” 伙计
Huh. It's "Pterodactyl," Man.
实际上  没人知道这个单词该怎么读
Actually, nobody knows how to pronounce it
因为没有人活在恐龙时代
Because no one was alive back in dinosaur days,
所以  呃
So, uh--
哇  差点从我头上碾过去
Whoa! Almost ran over my own head there.
梅宝  我们必须谈谈
Mabel, we've gotta talk.
这次任务的风险很高
This is a really high-stakes mission
我有点担心苏斯跟我们一起来
And I'm a little worried about Soos coming along on this one.
我很喜欢这家伙  但是有时他
I love the guy, but sometimes he...
成事不足  败事有余
Messes stuff up.
什么  什么时候
What?! Since when?
抱歉  伙计
Sorry, dude.
看  一个小精灵
Look! A fairy!
哈哈
Ha ha!
噢  抱歉  伙计  我把那小精灵弄死了
Oh, sorry, dude, I killed that fairy.
还是婉言拒绝他吧
Let him down easy.
这真太棒了  你和我  伙计
This is so great! You and me, bro!
最佳搭档
Best friends,
对抗恐龙  说不定还可以和它击掌
Fighting and potentially high-fiving dinosaurs.
苏斯  瞧  我必须告诉你一些事
Soos, look, I, uh... I gotta tell you something.
好的  但在告诉我之前
Okay, but before you do,
看看我给咱俩做的队服吧
check out these matching shirts I made for us.
这个家伙是谁
Who's this guy right here?
你  就是你  哥们儿
You. Totally you, dude.
这些光线代表着友谊
And these rays indicate friendship.
你刚才想告诉我什么来着
So what was it you were gonna tell me again?
呃  玉龙  我们来了
Uh... p-terodactyl, here we come!
太好了
Yes!
直面恐龙的兄弟
Bros before dinos!
好的  红色毛线指向
Okay, the red yarn leads to...
麦戈科特老头
Old Man McGucket?!
朋友们  你们好啊
Howdy, friends!
你在这儿做什么呢
What are you doing out here?
说了你也不会相信我的
You'll never believe me.
当我在演奏我的每小时乡间民乐时
So I was doing my hourly hootenanny--
哦  这个家伙
Ohh! This guy.
一个巨大的有着大翅膀的怪兽
When this enormous wingly critter
偷了我的器乐勺
Stole my musical spoons
而且极快地飞进了那被遗弃的矿场里
And flew lickety-split into the abandoned mines down yonder.
这下面看起来有点阴森啊
Looks kinda hairy down there.
来吧  斯坦叔公  你可以的
Come on, Grunkle Stan, you can handle it.
你一拳打到翼龙脸上了  不是吗
You punched a pterodactyl in the face, remember?
哦  是啊  哈哈
Oh, yeah. Ha ha.
我确实打了  不是吗
I did do that, didn't I?
我的天  真是令人怀疑的笑容
My! What suspicious laughter!
各位  我们要进去了
Guys, we're going in.
需要有人跟着你们
Need someone to tag along
再讲讲奇怪的个人趣事吗
and tell weird personal stories?
不  谢了
No, thanks.
那么有一次我
So there I am
和一只浣熊在为抢一块肉打斗时
Fightin' a raccoon for the same piece of meat,
我们的嘴巴越来越近  最后不小心亲在一起
When our mouths get close and we kiss accidentally.
你听不懂我的意思  是吗
Uhh. You can't take a hint, can you?
是的
Nope!
-老天爷  -难以置信
- Sweet moses! - Razzle dazzle!
真是棒极了
Fancy marmalade!
这些植物看起来  是侏罗纪时代的吧
These plants look all jurassic-y.
这个小家伙闻起来真像电池酸液啊
Huh. This little fella smells like battery acid.
感觉我已经失去嗅觉了
Looks like I lost my sense of smell. Ha ha ha!
哦  摇摇
Oh, Waddles,
我们一定会找到你的
We're gonna find you!
它们都被困在树脂里
They're all trapped inside tree sap!
就这样存活了六千五百万年
That's how they survived for 65 million years.
一定是滚滚热浪把它们烤化放出来了
The summer heat must be melting them loose!
我的天  玉米角兽一边去吧
Holy moly! Forget the cornicorn--
这可是永生难忘的奇观啊
This is the attraction of a lifetime!
我可以带人们下来
I could bring people down here
然后把这个地方变成主题公园
And turn this into some sort of theme park.
侏罗纪树脂洞
"Jurassic sap hole."
呃  大伙
Uh, dudes...
我们也许应该继续走吧
Maybe we should keep moving.
这可会成为金矿啊
This could be a gold mine!
天鹅绒绳子之类的放在那边
Velvety rope type deal there,
售票亭放在这里  哈哈
Ticket booth here--ha!
我应该早点把那头猪放外面去
I shoulda put that pig outside ages ago!
-等等  你刚说什么  -怎么了
- Wait. What did you just say? - Hmm? What's that?
你说恐龙飞进屋里的
You said the dinosaur flew into the house.
不  等等
No, wait. Uh--
-如果你这样想的话  -是你把摇摇放在外面的
- If you think about it - you put waddles outside,
然后你还骗了我
Then you lied to me about it!
现在好了  因为你  我的小猪可能死了
And now, thanks to you, my pig could be dead!
摇摇可能死了
Waddles could be dead!
呃  他是动物  他就该呆在外面
Look, he's an animal. He belongs outside.
不  够了
No! That's it!
斯坦叔公  我永远  再也不会和你说话了
Grunkle Stan, I am never, ever speaking to you again!
哎呀  你不会是认真的吧
Look, you can't be serious.
有人现在在说话吗  因为我根本听不见有人说话
Oh, is someone talking right now? Because I can't hear them!
小鬼
Kid!
我什么也听不见
I can't hear anyone!
没人和我说话
No one's talking to me!
大伙们  别吵了
Guys, guys, don't fight.
你们为什么就不能像我和迪普一样
Why can't you be more like me and Dipper?
好了  一切都会变好的
Look, everything's gonna be cool.
要找到这头猪我们只要跟着这些线就好了
All we gotta do to find the pig is follow this here yarn.
我们跟着走  跟着走
We just keep following and following,
当我们到达尽头
And when we reach the end--
是哪个洞穴来着
Wh-which cave was it again?
苏斯  你把路线弄丢了
Ohh, Soos! You lost the trail!
嘿  别担心  我们会找到路的  相信我
Hey, come on, we'll find our way. Trust me!
不好意思  伙计
Sorry, dude.
我受够了  看  这就是为什么我不想带你来的原因
That is it! See, this is why I didn't want to bring you along!
你  你什么意思
What--what do you mean?
我的意思是  这对梅宝很重要
I mean, this is really important to Mabel,
可是你却把所有事都搞砸了
And you keep screwing everything up!
你毁了我们的照片
You ruined our photograph,
现在你又让我们绝望地迷路了
And now you've got us hopelessly lost!
但我们是玉龙好兄弟啊  我还做了T恤
But we're p-terodactyl bros. I made t-shirts.
应该是  翼龙
It's pronounced "Pterodactyl."
而且这些T恤完全没用  它们像巨人一样大
And these shirts are useless! They're gigantic!
我的体型  不一样啊  伙计
I...have...A different. Body type, dude!
-这倒成了我的错  -我只是觉得  知道吗
- Oh, so it's my fault? - I just thought, ya know...
嘿  振作起来  伙计们
Hey! Cheer up, fellers!
我把你们的灯修好了
I fixed your lantern!
我们在干嘛啊
Heh heh! What-- what are we doin'?
都别做出突然的动作  也不要发出响声
Nobody make any sudden movements or loud noises.
耶  我们找到翼龙啦
Yeehah! We found a pterodactyl!
大伙  我们需要一个计划离开这里
Guys. We need a plan to get out of here.
有了  不如让梅宝给苏斯织一套猪猪服
Okay, okay. How's about Mabel knits Soos a pig costume...
我喜欢
I like it.
然后我们把苏斯当做活人献祭
And we use soos as a human sacrifice!
-我喜欢  -你觉得呢  梅宝
- I like it. - Whaddya say, mabel?
哎呀  别这样
Aw, come on,
你不可能永远不和我说话的
You can't stop talkin' to me forever.
是啊  梅宝  我们得团结协作才行
Yeah, Mabel, we have to work together here.
什么  你想和梅宝合作
What? You want to work with Mabel
而不是你的好兄弟苏斯
But not your buddy Soos?
等等  你们听到了吗
Wait! Did you hear that?
摇摇
Waddles!
-等等  孩子  -梅宝
- Wait, kid! - Mabel!
你疯了吗
Are you nuts?!
有人在说话吗
Oh, is someone speaking?
因为我什么都听不见哦
Because I can't hear anything!
哦不  她被恐惧吓聋了
Oh, no! She's gone deaf with fear!
梅宝  快回来
Mabel, come back here!
摇摇
Waddles!
哦  我的好摇摇
Oh! My waddles!
我再也不会失去你了
I'll never lose you again!
梅宝
Uh... Mabel?
嘘  你现在安全了
Sh-sh-sh. You're safe now.
梅宝  好了  你找到它了
Mabel, great, you got him.
现在我们得赶快走了
Now we gotta get out of here!
摇摇  等等
Waddles, wait!
从我身上下来  你个笨猪
Get off me, you dumb pig!
小心
Look out!
-哦不  -斯坦
- Oh, no! - Stan!
派恩斯先生
Mr. Pines!
哦  你倒是挺享受的
Yeah, you would enjoy this.
伙计们  我们得救他们
Guys, we've gotta save them!
麦戈科特  你有没有什么发明
McGucket, do you have an invention
可以分散翼龙的注意力
that can distract the pterodactyl?
我有吗
Do I?!
没有
Nope.
欢迎来到这个世界上  小伙计
Well, welcome to the world, little feller.
这个笨家伙肯定是饿坏了
The dumb thing must be hungry.
我猜不是你就是我了  笨猪
I guess it's you or me, pig.
你在看什么
What are you lookin' at?
别这样  别用那副表情看我
Aw, come on, don't give me that look.
那我该怎么办  让它吃了我
What am I supposed to do, let it eat me?
我知道了  你是想让我有歉疚感
Oh I get it! You're trying to guilt me.
那是没用的 伙计
Well, it ain't workin', pal.
谁在乎你是不是这世上梅宝最爱的东西啊
Who cares if you're mabel's favorite thing in the world?
我照样活得下去  即使没有那孩子一直和我说话
I can live without the kid talkin' to me all the time,
跟我讲她的笑话  逗我笑
Tellin' me her jokes... makin' me laugh...
啊  该死
Ah, dang it!
好吧  这肯定要成为我做过的最蠢的事了
Well, this is just about the dumbest thing I've ever done.
你想要这头猪
You want this pig?
那你就得先过我这关  你个会飞的恶魔
Then you're gonna have to get through me, you flying devil!
来抓我啊
Come and get me!!!
伙计们  它真的
Aw, dude. Did he really just
吃了那个探矿的家伙吗  这真是糟透了
eat that prospector guy? That is messed up!
我没事
I'm okay!
我们该怎么办  怎么办啊
What do we do? What do we do?
-我们得站成一列  -什么
- We have to get in a straight line. - What?!
翼龙的眼睛间隔很远
A pterodactyl's eyes are so far apart
如果你站在它的正前方  它就看不见你了
That if you stand right in front of it, it can't see you.
苏斯  今天你把所有事都弄砸了
Soos, you've been wrong about stuff all day.
-我们怎么可能  -伙计
- How can we... - Dude, look.
我知道我搞砸了很多事
I know I've messed up a lot.
我可能有点笨拙
I could be sorta clumsy,
而且也不像我想的那样可爱
And it's not always as loveable as I think.
但是拜托  作为我的朋友  这次就相信我吧
But please, as my friend, just trust me on this one.
站在我后面  大伙
Get behind me, dudes.
起作用了
It's working.
苏斯  你做到了
Soos, you did it!
难道那个是
Was that...
斯坦
Stan?
摇摇
Waddles!
他在打它的脸
He's punching him in the face!
我从地狱之心刺向你
From heck's heart I stab at thee!
棒极了  你还好吗  斯坦
Oh, yes! Ha ha! You're all right, Stan?
派恩斯先生  你没事
Oh, Mr. Pines, you're okay!
这是你的猪  孩子
Here's your pig, kiddo.
摇摇
Oooh! Waddles!
你为我救了他
Oh... you saved him for me!
是啊  好吧  有时候你只需要
Yeah, well, sometimes you just gotta--
小心
Look out!
我们被困住了
We're trapped!
快  这个喷泉能把我们打上去
Quick! The geyser can shoot us back up!
来吧  快啊  快
Come on, go! Go!
直面恐龙的兄弟
Bros before dinos!
我真不敢相信你为了摇摇做了那么多
I can't believe you did all that for Waddles!
好吧  我可受不了最爱的侄孙女不和我说话
Ah, well, I can't have my favorite niece not talking to me,
就算是要我跳上一只翼龙  狠狠地打它的脸
And if I gotta leap onto a pterodactyl and punch him in the face,
那我也得去啊
Then that's what I gotta do.
（注：sappy也有“多汁”的意思）
那可有点傻啊
That's kinda sappy.
什么  那可是我的真情实感
What?! That's how I feel!
不是  我的意思是
No, I mean...
哦  是啊
Oh, yeah.
弄到你了
Gotcha!
你看看  那家伙毁了我的马甲
Check it out, that thing destroyed my vest.
苏斯  快看
Soos, look!
是真正的恐龙牙齿  真是太棒了
A real dinosaur tooth? That's awesome!
还是你把我们从那里救出来更棒
Not as awesome as you saving us back there.
翼龙好兄弟
Pterodactyl bros?
Pterodactyl bros.
嘿  我刚才的发音对了
Hey, I pronounced it right that time.
觉得我们该担心其他那些恐龙吗
Think we need to worry about the rest of those dinosaurs?
也许吧
I doubt it.
我从恐龙里吃出了一条生路
I ate my way through a dinosaur!
你好  我是鲍比・伦佐比
Hi, I'm Bobby Renzobbi!
你的手臂嫉妒你的腿吗
Are your arms jealous of your legs?
那你就需要手臂裤
Then you need arm pants--
穿在手臂上的裤子
The pants that you wear on your arms!
啧啧  谁会真买这种电视导购节目里的东西啊
Sheesh. Who actually buys this infomercial stuff?
我也觉得  不是吗
Ha. I know, right?
取消订单  取消订单
Cancel the order. Cancel the order!
（注：tell, fold, bluff 均为德州扑克术语）
吭吭哧哧  他露出马脚了
Snorting. That's his tell.
-我弃牌  -坏运气  笨蛋
- I fold. - Tough luck, sucker.
-摇摇只是虚张声势而已  -什么
- Waddles was bluffing. - What?!
我有四张A呢
I had four aces!
这猪真是个巫师
That pig is a wizard!
快看他  他在嘲笑我呢
Look at him. He's taunting me.
我在最后八轮里出了老千
I've been cheating the last eight turns.
哈哈  这才是我的好女孩
Ha ha! That's my girl.